<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Priority Manager</name>
  <author>P4RAD0X</author>
  <packageId>p4rad0x.prioritymanager</packageId>
  <modVersion>1.3.0</modVersion>
  <description>Automatically assigns work priorities to colonists based on their skills, user-defined roles, health status, and actual work needs. 

Features:
- Auto-assign priorities based on colonist skills
- Optional role presets (Researcher, Doctor, Farmer, etc.) or fully automatic best-job detection
- **NEW: Custom Roles** - create your own roles with drag-and-drop job ordering and importance levels (Disabled, VeryLow, Low, Normal, High, Critical)
- **NEW: Tabbed Mod Settings** - Global settings and custom role editor accessible from mod options menu
- Intelligent secondary job assignment (priorities 2-4)
- Need-based assignment - prioritizes jobs with active work (bills, construction, harvesting, etc.)
- Improved idle detection - automatically assigns more jobs to idle colonists
- Illness/injury response: reduces workload for sick colonists
- Solo colonist survival mode: prioritizes essential tasks
- Periodic auto-recalculation or manual control
- Integrates directly into the Work tab
- Min/Max worker controls per job type (absolute or percentage-based)
- Compatible with Complex Jobs mod (auto-detects specialized work types)
- Compatible with PriorityMaster mod (extends to 1-99 priority range)
- Composite roles with multi-job workflows (Builder, Demolition, Medic, Industrialist)

Set a colonist's primary role or let the system figure out their best jobs automatically! The system now intelligently focuses on work that actually needs doing.

Compatibility: Works with Complex Jobs, PriorityMaster, and any mod that adds custom work types.</description>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.6</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    <li>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</li>
    <li>FrozenSnowFox.ComplexJobs</li>
    <li>Lauriichan.PriorityMaster</li>
  </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>

